

**My Contact** 

gkhundadze@gmail.com

www.gkhundadze.com

+995 574-405-188

Tbilisi, Georgia

**Hard Skill** 

Bootstrap / Tailwind

HTML / XMLSCSS / SASS / LESS

Javascript

**Soft Skill** 

TeamworkProblem Solving

CommunicationMulti-tasking

• Programming Concepts

React

• Npm

AngularVueGithub

# Grigori <u>Khundadze</u>

## Front-End Developer

### **About Me**

I am a frontend developer with a passion for creating beautiful and functional websites. My journey began in 2020 when I started learning HTML,CSS and JAVASCRIPT at Geolab, a leading technology education center. I was fascinated by the possibilities that these technologies offered, and I worked hard to master them.

## **Professional Experience**

#### **Stars Georgia**

2021 - 2022

Front-End Developer

#### Unilab

2022 - 2023

Front-End Development Mentor / Lecturer

#### Geolab

2023 - Present

- Lecturer assistant / Javascript React
- Administrator

#### Georgian education management information system

2022 - 2023

Javascript Course Co-author

# Education Background

- GeolabHTML, CSSCompleted in 2021
- geolab
   Javasctript / Angular 2+
   Completed in 2021
- Unilab
   Acceleration program Front-End

  Completed in 2022

## **Projects**

Terms Base

**Una Chatbot** 

E207 Room

**Volga Interior** 

From Chaos To Cosmos

<u>Mysanteknik</u>